我帮你们准备了一份礼物
Hey, I got you a present!
天啊  你之前把它藏在哪里了
Oh, my goodness, where did you hide it?
我几周前订了当做你们结婚的礼物
I got it for your wedding and I ordered it weeks ago,
现在终于送来了
and it finally got here!
菲比  你不必送我们结婚礼物
Pheebs, you didn't have to get us anything
你已经唱过...
for our wedding you already sang...
我喜欢  好大啊  快打开吧
I love it! It's huge! Let's open it! Let's open it!
是"吃豆小姐"的游戏机  我的天啊
It's a Ms. PacMan machine!  Oh, my God!
我不知道该放到哪里  就暂时放在客厅了
I didn't know where to put it, so I just left it here for now.
我们可以把它放在客房  好吧
We can put it in the guest bedroom.  Yeah, okay.
我觉得放在这里挺好
I kind of like it here.
你真的喜欢吗
Do you really like it?
开什么玩笑  我小时候整天待在游乐场里
Are you kidding?! I practically spent my entire childhood at the arcade.
这是我第二喜欢的游戏
This is like...Oh my, this is like my second favorite game!
你最喜欢什么
Really? What's your first?
我记不得名字了
I don't remember the name of it.
内容是什么
Well, what did it do?
把铜板放进去  拉把手
You'd put a quarter in, pull some handles
就能拿到糖果
and win a candy bar or something.
自动贩卖机
A vending machine?
别可怜我  每次我都会赢
Don't feel bad for me. I won every time!
《老友记》  第八季  第12集  乔伊和瑞秋约会
Friends S08E12 The One Where Joey Dates Rachel
我很高兴你们都在
I'm so glad you guys are here.
我等不及要告诉大家
I've been dying to tell someone
古生物系今天的新闻了
what happened in the paleontology department today.
你觉得他看到了我们吗  还有机会溜走吗
Do you think he saw us, or can we still slip out?
系主任诺曼教授要退休了  所以...
Professor Newman, the department head, is retiring, so...
你升职系主任了
They made you head of the department!
不  我要接手他其中一门高级课
No, I get to teach one of his advanced classes!
我为什么没当上系主任
Why didn't I get head of the department?
瑞秋  我有个重要约会
Hey, Rach, listen, I got a big date coming up.
你知道哪家餐厅不错吗
Do you know a good restaurant?
保罗餐厅  那里东西好吃  气氛又很浪漫
Paul's Cafe. It's got great food and it's really romantic.
太棒了  谢谢
Great, thanks.
然后带她到四季饭店喝东西
Then afterward you can take her to the Four Seasons for drinks.
或是到城里听爵士乐
Or go downtown and listen to some jazz.
或是跳舞  带她去跳舞吧
Or dancing. Oh, take her dancing!
你真的很会拖延性爱的进度
You sure are naming a lot of ways to postpone sex.
我怀念约会的感觉  可以盛装打扮
I miss dating. Getting all dressed up
去高级餐厅吃饭
and going to a fancy restaurant.
我很久都没法再出去约会了
I won't be able to do that for so long.
那真的很有趣
And it's so much fun.
其实坐在这里
Not that sitting at home worrying about
担心生孩子的事也挺有意思
giving birth to a sixteen pound baby is not fun.
这样吧  我带你出去约会
Hey, you know what? Why don't I take you out.
什么  你可不想跟孕妇约会
What? Joey, you don't want to date a pregnant lady.
我愿意  我们就出去好好享受一番
Yes, I do. We're gonna go out, we're gonna have a good time.
我会让你忘了生孩子  剖腹产
I'll take your mind off of childbirth, and Csections...
宝宝的头撑大...
...and gaint baby heads stretching out...
好吧  我答应你  我跟你去
Okay, I'll go with you. I'll go with you.
会很好玩的  好吧
It will be fun.  All right.
不要  太棒了
No, no! Yes!
快来看啊  莫妮卡
Would you look at that, Monica.
我打败了你的最佳成绩  真可惜
I just knocked off all your top scores. How sad.
好吧  轮到我了
Okay, I'm next.
别再开始新一盘了  轮到我了  菲比
Don't start another game. I'm next! Phoebe?
抱歉  我赢得太开心  听不到你说话
Sorry, I couldn't hear you over all the winning.
菲比在霸占游戏机
Chandler, Phoebe's hogging the game.
至于吗  不过是个愚蠢的游戏
Who cares? It's a stupid game.
你觉得它蠢是因为你玩得太逊
You only think it's stupid because you suck at it.
我不逊  是游戏太逊
I don't suck. It sucks.
你才逊
You suck.
如果这个游戏
Wait okay, if this game
会惹得你们俩闹别扭
is gonna cause problems between the two of you,
那我还是自己留着玩吧
then maybe I should just keep it.
不  我喜欢它  这个礼物棒极了
No, I love it. It is a great present.
你为什么不回家等我给你寄感谢贺卡呢
In fact, why don't you go home and wait for the thankyou card?
你为什么这么想玩这个游戏
Why do you want to play this game so badly?
是啊  又不是每玩完一盘就往外吐糖果
Yeah! It's not like it spits out a Clark bar after every game.
好吧  菲比  够了  快起来
Okay. Phoebe, that's it. Come on, out of the chair.
快点  快点  起来
Come on. Come on, out of the chair.
菲比
Phoebe!
乔伊  麻烦你去开门
Joey, could you get that?
乔伊
Joey.
你怎么在这儿
What are you doing here?
我以为你在房里
I thought you were in your room.
我是来接你去约会的
No, I'm picking you up for our date.
这是送你的
These are for you.
百合花  这是我最喜欢的花  谢谢
Lilies. They're my favorite. Thank you.
还有巧克力布朗尼
And a brownie.
只剩一半了
Well, half a brownie.
其实只剩袋子了
Actually, it's just a bag.
从花店走回来真的很远
It's a long walk from the flower shop
我饿得头晕  所以...
and I felt faint, so...
这简直太棒了  我觉得好像真的在约会
This is so great! I actually feel like I'm on a real date.
不过我有种要晨吐的感觉
Although, I have a hint of morning sickness,
而且我穿的内裤裤腰高到
and I'm wearing underwear that goes up to about...
这里
...there.
少来了  这就是真正的约会
Hey, come on. This is a real date.
你家好漂亮
So nice place you got here.
桌上足球  披萨盒
Foosball. Pizza box.
还有花花公子杂志  你是我喜欢的那种女人
Oh, a subscription to Playboy. My kind of woman.
那是我室友的杂志
That's my roommate's.
我想见见他  他似乎是个好男人
I'd like to meet him. He sounds like a standup guy.
但他对我的保护欲很强  你最好小心一点
But he's protective of me, so you'd better watch yourself.
你室友很帅吗
So this roommate of yours, is he goodlooking?
你一定要很努力才能控制自己不爱上他
Must be tough to keep your hands off him.
我很确定他是男同志
I'm pretty sure he's gay.
他才不是呢  你为什么要破坏这个游戏
No! No, he's not! Why are you trying to ruin the game?
别这样嘛
Come on.
这就又回到了葛瑞利的骨牌理论
Which brings us back, of course, to Greely's Theory of Dominance.
今天的课就到这里
That's it for today.
有人知道费利曼楼在哪里吗
Does anyone know where the Freeman Building is?
那是A大道的新大楼
Yeah. It's the new building on Avenue A.
什么  那在城里的另一边
Waht? That's all the way across town.
我十分钟内得赶到那里给研究生上课
I'm supposed to teach a graduate seminar there in ten minutes.
那是不可能的
Dude, that's not gonna happen.
快闪开
Move it! Move it! Move it!
我是老师
Hey! I'm the teacher!
大家好
Hello.
抱歉我迟到了  严重迟到了
Sorry I'm a little late. Whoa, a lot late.
我从自我介绍开始吧
Well, let me start by introducing myself.
我是盖勒教授
I'm Professor Geller.
总而言之...
So to sum up...
我是盖勒教授  今天大家表现很好
...I'm Professor Geller. Good job today.
菲力牛排搭配什么
Now the filet mignon, what comes with that?
配菜是蒸蔬菜
There's a side of steamed vegetables.
除了蔬菜...
Instead of the vegetables...
我可以用什么菜品搭配
...is there any way that I could substitute the...
三磅龙虾行吗
...threepound lobster?
帮她把两道菜都送上来
You know what? Bring her both.
我跟她点一样的东西
And I'll have the same.
感觉这次约会很成功
Wow, this is shaping up to be a pretty good date.
我差点忘了  我没付你房租
I almost forgot. I didn't pay you the rent check.
别当我们是室友  我们在约会
No roommate stuff, okay? We're on a date.
我就要知道乔伊·崔比安尼是怎么跟人约会的了
Okay. Wow, so I get to see what Joey Tribbiani is like on a date.
你有什么招数吗
Do you have any moves?
不  我只会做我自己
No, I'm just myself,
如果她们不喜欢我
and if they don't like me for...
抱歉  这种话我实在说不下去
I'm sorry, I couldn't even get through that.
我就知道  告诉我你有什么招数
I knew it. I knew it. Come, tell me your moves.
好吧
All right.
约会一开始  我会假装有影迷
I usually start by having a bottle of wine
送红酒给我
sent to my table from a fan.
天啊  这招管用吗
Oh, my God. And that works?
你得加上一句"真是太不好意思了
Well, it does when you combine it with, "This is so embarrassing,
我只想过正常人的生活"
I just want to have a normal life!"
你们这些可怜的名人
You poor little famous man.
好吧  听听这招
Okay, how about this one?
我本来想等到送你回家再吻你...
I was gonna wait until the end of the night to kiss you...
但你真的太美了  我实在难以自持
...but you're just so beautiful, I don't think I can.
天啊
Oh, my God!
这招太绝了  我差点就凑上去了  真的
Wow, that was fantastic! I almost leaned in. I really almost did.
告诉我你用的是什么招数
All right. So tell me one of your moves.
好吧
All right.
你是在哪里长大的
So where'd you grow up?
那就是你的招数
That's your move?
瑞秋  还好你长得很美
Boy, Rach, you're lucky you're hot.
快回答我的问题  皇后区
Come on, just answer the question.  Queens.
你跟父母亲近吗
So were you close to your parents?
我跟妈妈亲  跟爸爸不太说话
With my mom. Not so much my dad.
为什么
Why not?
我不知道  感觉我们之间有种隔阂
I don't know. I guess there's just always been this distance.
我们都假装没有  但事实上不然
I mean we both try to pretend it's not there, but it is.
那一定很辛苦
It's gotta be rough.
对  真的很辛苦  有时候我觉得...
Yeah, it's really tough. Sometimes I think...
太帅了
Nice move!
"你在哪里长大的 "  这招好简单啊
"Where'd you grow up?" So simple.
谢谢
Thank you.
对不起  我要去洗手间
Now, excuse me. I'm gonna use the restroom.
你在注视我离开的背影
Now you're watching me walk away.
没错  太简单了
Yes, I am! Again, so simple!
你一定不相信今天我做了什么
You are not gonna believe what I did today.
很明显  你没洗澡  也没刮胡子
It clearly wasn't showering or shaving.
我玩了一整天这个游戏  现在我是第一名
I got good. I played this game all day, and now I rule at it.
他们应该把它改名为"钱德勒小姐"
They should change the name to "Ms. Chandler."
还是不要好了
Although, I hope they don't.
你待在家里玩了一整天"吃豆小姐"
Wait a minute. You stayed home and played Ms. PacMan
而我在外面像牛一样工作
while I went to work like a chump?
我包办了前十名  把菲比挤下了排行榜
I got all the top 10 scores. I erased Phoebe off the board.
击掌庆祝一下吧
Highfive!
你的手是怎么了
What is the matter with your hand?
我打了八小时的电动
I've been playing it for like eight hours,
会放松下来的  看看我的比分记录
It'll loosen up. Come on. Check out the scores.
再看看我编的名字  全是脏话
Also, look at the initials. They're dirty words.
钱德勒  你为什么要那么做
Chandler, why would you do that?
因为这样很帅气
Because it's awesome.
你觉得那么做很聪明吗
You think it's clever?
我只能写下三个字母
They only give you three letters,
除了ASS（屁股）外  其它名字很难想
so after ASS, it is a challenge.
这不是脏话
This one's not dirty.
把它跟那个连在一起就是了
It is when you put it together with that one.
如果你不办法把它清掉
If you don't clear this off,
以后就别想从我这里尝到那种甜头
you won't get one of those from me.
本明天会过来玩游戏  不能让他看到这个
Ben's coming over tomorrow to play this game. This can't be there.
他都不知道这些词是什么意思
Come on. He won't know what they mean.
钱德勒  他都七岁了  他又不笨
Chandler, he's 7, he's not stupid.
最近你跟他谈过吗
Have you talked to him lately?
我要把插头拔掉
I'm gonna unplug it.
别啊  拔掉之后  我今天就等于一无所获
Nonono, if you unplug it, I'll have nothing to show for my day!
那和上班又有什么区别
It would be like I was at work.
不
No!
你看  记录还在
Hey, look! It's still there!
这玩意一定是用的原始记忆晶片
This thing must have some kind of primitive ROM chip or something!
你得打败自己的成绩
Honey, you gotta beat your scores.
我的手指都张不开了
With the claw?
好吧  让我来  我得把这些词消掉
Fine, I'll do it. I've just got to get this off the screen.
卡罗尔还在气你教他"拉我的手指"
Carol's still upset that you taught him "Pull my finger."
拉我的手指  我的手都毁了
Pull my finger. My hand is messed up!
我不会回答那个问题
I am not gonna answer that.
来吧  快挑一个
Oh, come on. Just pick one.
在莫妮卡  菲比  钱德勒跟罗斯之间...
Between Monica, Phoebe, Chandler and Ross...
如果你迫不得已
...if you had to, if you had to,
你会打谁
who would you punch?
我们是朋友  我不会打他们
No one! We're friends. I wouldn't punch any of them.
钱德勒吗
Chandler?
对  但我不知道为什么
Yeah, but I don't know why.
我玩得很开心  我也是
I'm having such a wonderful time!  Me too!
这是我最棒的约会经验  我知道
Rach, can I just say this is the best date I ever had.  I know!
我笑得好厉害
I've never laughed so hard.
你看到酒从我鼻子喷出来吗
Did you see the wine come out of my nose?
乔伊  我想大家都看到了
Joey, I think everybody saw the wine come out of your nose.
我从不知道自己会这么喜欢
I gotta say, I never knew I could enjoy
没有性爱的约会
the nonsex part of a date so much.
那是因为你没有跟我约会过
That's because you have never been on a date with me before.
好吧  别瞧不起我
All right. Now don't judge me.
通常我会等我的对象离开了再这么做
I normally wait till my date leaves,
但你住在这里  我要吃带回来的剩饭了
but but you live here. I'm ripping into this swan.
好吧  你也别瞧不起我
Okay, then you don't judge me.
我要去舔之前那个蛋糕的包装纸
I'm gonna suck on the cellophane from that brownie I had before.
对
Oh, yeah.
告诉我
So tell me,
乔伊·崔比安尼说晚安的招数是什么
what are Joey Tribbiani's endofthenight moves?
如果我想让那个女孩吻我...
Well, if I want the girl to kiss me...
首先我会让我的嘴巴看起来难以抵抗
...first thing I do is make my lips look irresistible.
你都是怎么做的
How do you do that?
你不能告诉任何人  但是
Now you can't tell anyone, but...
我会涂上护唇膏
...I put on shiny lip balm.
天啊  女人就跟飞蛾扑火一样
Oh, my God.  Like a moth to a flame, I'm telling you.
好吧  轮到你了
Okay, all right, so, now you go.
不  我不想告诉你
No, I don't want to tell you.
为什么  那太丢脸了
Why not?  Because it's embarrassing.
比涂黑莓口味的护唇膏还丢脸
More embarrassing than shiny raspberry lip balm?
我刚刚没说黑莓口味吧
I didn't say raspberry before, did I?
快告诉我  瑞秋
Just tell me, Rach. Just tell me.
好吧
Okay.
站起来
All right, stand up.
我们走到门口时...
Well, when we're at the door...
我会将我的嘴唇轻轻压在他的嘴唇上
...I lightly press my lips against his.
将身体靠向他  停留一秒钟
Then move into his body, just for a second.
然后我会发出这样的声音
And then I make this sound:
听起来没什么  但很有效
It doesn't sound like anything, but I swear it works.
对  的确有效
Oh, yeah. That would work, yeah.
好吧  我得睡了 我今晚玩得很开心
All right, I gotta go to bed. Honey. I had such a wonderful time.
我也是
Me too.
你上课迟到了50分钟  你是用爬的吗
You were 50 minutes late to the class, what did you crawl there?
不  我用跑的  真的很远
No, I ran, okay? It's really far.
现在的人怎么都听不懂
When did people stop understanding
"别挡我的路"呢
the phrase "Get the hell out of my way"?
你为什么不搭计程车
Why didn't you take a cab?
塞车太严重  还净是单行道
Between the traffic that time of day and all the oneway streets
搭计程车得花两倍的时间
it'd take me twice as long.
再说  我一星期有三堂课
Besides, I teach the class three times a week.
你以为我是富家子弟吗
Who am I, Rockefeller?
你不能再继续这样下去了
You won't be able to keep doing this.
没办法  不然他们会取消我这堂课
I have to. If I don't, they'll take the class away from me.
我已经把这条新闻登在我家的通讯报上了
And I put it in my family newsletter.
什么  你看过的  《盖勒通讯报》
Your what?  You've seen it, The Geller Yeller.
对
Right. Wow.
我想出一条比较快的路线
I think I figured out a much faster route.
我敢说这次我能及时赶到
I'm sure I can make it this time.
只是我不能害怕被车子撞到
I just can't be afraid to get a little bit hit by cars.
还记得昨晚我们谈过《狂犬惊魂记》吗
Remember last night when we talked about Cujo?
我不敢相信你没看过《狂犬惊魂记》
Yeah, I still can't believe you haven't seen Cujo.
真搞不懂你
What is wrong with you?
至于吗  那又不是《公民凯恩》
Relax, it's not like it's Citizen Kane.
你看完了《公民凯恩》
Have you ever sat through Citizen Kane?
是啊  真的很无聊  但那可是经典
Yeah, it's really boring. But it's, like, a big deal.
总之  我想去租《狂犬惊魂记》
Anyway, I was thinking about renting Cujo sometime.
我们今晚一起看吧
Yeah, all right. Well, let's do it tonight.
你不是有约会吗  对
Don't you have that big date tonight?  Oh, right.
乔伊  我能问你一件事吗  问吧
Hey, Joey, can I ask you something?  Yeah.
昨晚约会后  你有没有觉得怪怪的
After our date last night, did you feel a little weird?
天啊  你也是吗
Oh, my God. You did too?
我吓坏了  那是怎么回事
It totally freaked me out. What was that?
我不知道
I don't know.
我觉得应该是龙虾的问题
I'm kind of thinking it was the lobster.
对啊  龙虾
Oh, yeah. Yeah, the lobster.
我吐了一整晚  我也是
I was up sick all night.  Me too. All night.
真的吗  那我怎么没看到你
Really? How come we didn't cross paths?
对  那是因为
Yeah, well, that's because...
我都待在房里
...I stayed in my room.
我的洗衣篮惨不忍睹
You don't want to look in my hamper.
好了  吃掉那个
Okay, I got that.
躲过那里  然后再回来
I'll escape there. I'll come back here.
好了  加油  吃豆小姐
All right. Come on, Ms. PacMan.
你就是个小贱人  对吧
Well, you're just a little bitch, aren't you?!
大家好
Hey, you guys?
抱歉之前我霸占着电动玩具
I'm sorry that I was hogging the game before.
天啊
Oh, my God!
你朋友名字的缩写真难听
Your friends have some unfortunate initials.
那都是钱德勒干的
They're all Chandler.
钱德勒不可能有这么厉害
Chandler sucks. He couldn't get this good.
我很厉害  但那是要付出代价的
I did. But it came at a price.
本今晚要过来  不能让他看到这些
Ben's coming over tonight, and he can't see this.
七岁的孩子应该连杂交都看过了吧
Come on. By age 7, kids have already seen orgies.
还是只有我而己
Was it just me?
我办到了  我及时赶到了
Yes, I made it! I'm on time!
好了  请大家
Okay, why don't we all...
翻到第23页...
...open our books to page 23...
你们...
...where...
你们将会看到...
...where you will see...
很多红点
...a bunch of red spots.
请大家先看一会书  我要...
Okay, why don't you all start to read while I...
你没事吗  你似乎有点心不在焉
Are you all right? You seem a little distracted.
不  我没事  我只是
No, no, I'm fine. It's just...
我能问你一件事吗
Hey, can I ask you something?
你有没有这样的经验  看着你熟悉的人...
Have you ever looked at someone you know for a while
突然间有不一样的感觉
and suddenly seen them in a different way?
你是说从背后看吗
You mean like from behind?
没错  就是那样
Yeah. That's exactly it.
有一次  我从背后看这个家伙
You know what? One time I saw this guy from behind
觉得他真的很普通
and he seemed like a totally normal guy
他一转身  才发现他是史蒂芬·鲍德温
And then he turned around and it was Stephen Baldwin!
对
Yeah.
你完全了解我的意思
So you know exactly what I'm talking about.
没错
Totally!
我要失陪一会  请便
Would you excuse me for a sec?  Yeah. Sure.
菲比  你真的很厉害  我知道
Oh, my god. Phoebe! You're on fire!  I know!
就差一分了  你能行的
One more score to go. You can do it!
别碰我  别碰她
Don't touch me!  Don't touch her!
左边  左边  右边  右边
Go left! Go left! Go right! Go right!
我做不到
I can't! I can't!
不  你这个天杀的...
No! You son of a...
菲比
Phoebe?!
本  别看机器
Oh, hi, Ben. No, don't look at the machine!
谢天谢地你回来了  我在看《狂犬惊魂记》
Thank God you're home! I'm watching Cujo.
你一个人  对  这只狗是怎么了
Alone?  Yes! What is wrong with this dog?
你看到他们被困在车里
Did you get to the part where they're trapped in the car
库裘自己去撞车的那一幕了吗
and Cujo's throwing himself at the windshield?
没有  说真的  这只狗有什么毛病
No, seriously, what's wrong with the dog?
等一下  你怎么这么早就回来了
Wait a minute, what are you doing home so early?
你不是去约会了吗
What happened to your date?
我们之间不来电
Oh, it didn't work out.
你要跟我一起把电影看完吗
Do you want to watch the rest of the movie with me?
好吧
Oh, okay. Yeah.
我以前从未对一部电影有这种感觉
You know, I never thought I'd say this about a movie,
但我真希望这只狗死掉
...but I really hope this dog dies.
你坐在那里干嘛  坐在这里保护我
What are you doing over there? Come sit here, you protect me.
没问题  有何不可呢
Oh. Sure, yeah. Why not?
好吧
Okay.
那就是他
Okay. That's him, that's him!
那就是库裘  我知道
That's Cujo! That's Cujo!  I know.
没事的
It's gonna be okay.
天啊  他现在又要干嘛  我不敢看
Oh, my God. What's he gonna do now? I can't watch.
你怎么能看得下去  你不害怕吗
Seriously, how can you watch this? aren't you scared?
我怕极了
Terrified.
大家都到了吗
So is everybody here?
今天我提早到了
I got here a little early, myself.
开始上课吧
Let us begin.
海德罗恐龙主要
Now, the hadrosaurids have been unearthed
分布在两个地方
in two main locations.
这里...
Here...
跟...
...and...
这里
...here.
至于水龙...
Now, as for the hydrosaurs...